Ankita Kaushik

Software Developer



- ankita.kaushik012@gmail.com
- **4** 64-2109053789
- Hamilton, New Zeland
- in linkedin/ankitakaushik
- codingNinjas/ankita012
- github.com/Ankita012

CKILLE

• medium/ankita012

C++		
.Net		
JavaScript •		
Reactjs		
HTML & CSS		
Tailwind •		
Bootstrap •		
S LANGUAGES		
English •		
Hindi		
♂ INTERESTS		

Cooking, Listening Songs,

Meditation

PROFILE

As a software developer with 3 years of experience, My proficiency lies in ReactJS, HTML, Tailwind CSS, and.NET Core. I have a passion for creating intuitive and user-friendly interfaces that enhance the user experience. With my expertise and dedication, I strive to deliver high-quality solutions that meet client requirements.

EDUCATION

B.Tech, *O P Jindal University* 06/2015 – 05/2019 | India CGPA- 9.19/10

12th, CBSE, *O.P Jindal School* 04/2013 – 05/2014 | Raigarh, India

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer, Saeloun

05/2022 - 04/2023 | Pune, India

- Worked on mobile app gaining skill in react native.
- Worked on internal projects like Miru, Tlatoani, and company's website.
- Also written blog in the front-end category.

Software Engineer, Tarento Group

06/2021 - 05/2022 | Bengaluru, India

- Worked on the project Aastrika
- Worked as a productive and positive team member to design, code, test, report, and debug.
- Managed front-end with mobile responsiveness and integration with back-end development in the project.

Software Developer, Techment Technology

06/2019 - 08/2020 | Bhilai, C.G, India

- Worked as a Front-end developer on projects like chooseavo, windsorvineyards, mydoctorslive, Techment's website.
- Worked on internal and external projects with great care of responsiveness.

♣ INTERNSHIP/TRAINING

Interbiz Consultancy

01/2019 – 02/2019 | Bilaspur Design and testing on live projects of protocol now App

CHIPS

05/2018 - 06/2018 | Raipur

Worked with investment promotion team and created RFP document for morNivesh

O.P Jindal University

05/2017 – 06/2017 | Raigarh Web Development